ADRIANA HEESH

Junior Developer

About Me

With a degree in Marketing, and previous experience in eCommerce and social media, I have skills in graphic design, communications and user experience. I'm excited to combine this experience and my developer skills to front-end projects.

Education

Diploma of Information Technology - 2020 - 2021

Coder Academy

Notable projects:

Collaborated with peers on 'Bored App' project (see my Portfolio) using Git feature branches, and managing pull requests and merge conflicts. Project managed in Agile style utilising Trello boards.

Two-sided market place 'Soilmates' built with Ruby on Rails. I learned so much about database management and table/relationship planning in this project.

Bachelor of Business (Marketing) - 2017

Queensland University of Technology

Professional Experience

Maternity Leave - Dec 2020 - Jul 2021

Marketing Assistant - PQ Collection

January 2019 - May 2020

As Marketing Assistant I was responsible for social media and website management, including content creation, influencer relationship management and copywriting. I also assisted in campaign creation and execution across marketing channels. In this role, I

- executed a rebrand and assisted in the launch of a new website with an external agency
- created new conversions by expanding social presence into other platforms
- maintained above average conversion rates on online store
- implemented a 'Shop by Shape' filter to enhance user experience
- established Instagram and Facebook to be in the top 3 traffic sources for conversions

Skills

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React

Ruby/Ruby on Rails

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD